Guide to the North American 19th century theatre broadside collection, 1850-1867
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: Canada and New York City, 1855-1867
  - Wallack's Theatre Broadside (New York), October 11, 1855 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "Lavater"-or-"Not a Bad Judge", "500 (Pounds) reward", "How Stout you're Getting", "The Spitalfields Weaver", "A Lady in Difficulties", "Mrs. Johnston"-or-"What's in a Name?", "The Game of Love".
  - Metropolitan Theatre Broadside(New York), October 15, 1855 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Benefit of MLE Rachel, Mme. A. De La Grange, "Le Depit Amoreux", "Joan of Arc", French national hymn: "La Marseillaise", Rachel's plays and biographies on sale at Hall and Sons in New York, opera glasses lent on hire, "Lady Tartuffe", "Adrienne Lecovreur".
  - Burton's Broadside (New York), October 12, 1855 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Mr. Burton, "Serious Family", "Toodles", "Still Water Runs Deep", "Daughter of the Regiment", "John of Paris", G. Jordan, Miss Kate Reignolds.
  - Lorimier Hall Broadside, April 11, 1856 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Mr. H. Van Liew, Mr. W.S. Forrest, "Maid of Crissey"-or-"Conscripts of 1812", "Perfection"-or the-"Maid of Munster", "Irish Tutor"-or the-"New Lights", desiring to make theatre worthy of public patronage.
- Series 7: Boston and New York City, 1850s-1860s
  This series contains four broadsides of performances at City Hall in Boston, Niblo's Garden in New York, and performances by the Kimball Dramatic Association at City Hall in Boston. Size of broadsides range from 5"x8 1/3" to 6 1/2"x14".
  - Kimball Dramatic Association at City Hall Broadside (Boston), March 12, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Exhibition of the Kimball Dramatic Association, "Golden Farmer", "Swiss Cottage", L.T. Gardner, W.C. Berry, J.H. Brown.
  - City Hall Broadside (Boston), June 15, 1850s-1860s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Last night of "Little Wonders", Benefit of Little Ellen, "Richard 3d", Ellen Batemean, Kate Bateman, "Napoleon's Old Guard", Mr. Bateman, "The FOx and the Wolf", strict order will be observed.
  - City Hall Broadside (Boston), June 18, 1850s-1860s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Grand Festival, Benefit of Mr. Vincent, Kate and Ellen Bateman - the infant wonders, Miss Lucy Western, Miss Helen Western, "Lady of Munster", "Macbeth", "Bombastes Furioso", "Loan of a Lover".
  - Niblo's Garden Broadside (New York), 1850s-1860s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    G.F. Bristow, "Rip Van Winkle", Pyne and Harrison Opera Co., orchestral performance, scenery synopsis, books for sale in Garden, 20 minute intermission for promenade.